BGM
Hello. I'm Ayame Tsutsui. This is Sakura Endo.
We're here today for the school festival.
They were looking for people who were interested in coming to the festival.
It seems we got a lot of applications, but this time we went to Tama Art University.
Thank you very much.
First time at a school festival? First time! I've been to my sister's high school festival, but it's a college.
Also, it seems like a lot of the people who do jacket photos and design here at Tama Art University are from here.
I'd like to go there today and have some fun.
I'd like to say hello to the people who applied and to the people who are interested in this event.
Hello, I'm Kaburagi, the chairperson of the Hama Art University Art Festival Committee.
I'm Kasahara, in charge of the flea market. I'm Nemoto, who applied this time.
I'm Nemoto.
By the way, why did you apply?
I like Nogizaka, of course.
But I also wanted to let people who are not interested in art know about the Hamami Art Festival.
Thank you very much. I'm looking forward to it.
We are all classmates.
I'm the same age as Kaburagi-kun.
I love what you and Endo did together.
I see.
I'm 20 now.
The same age.
I'm so glad.
I didn't even realize I was younger than you.
That's right.
I'm getting younger and younger.
This is the Design Building. The attraction of this university is the exhibitions.
Many of the exhibits are things that students usually make for their assignments, or things that they make individually.
Many of them are made by individual students, so there are many of them on display.
This time, I'd like to show you the exhibition of the students of the Graphic Design Department.
Yes, please.
I look forward to working with you.
Oh, I'll do it.
I didn't know there were so many of them.
Wow.
There are so many different kinds.
Oh, wow.
Wow.
That's amazing.
It's kind of cute.
It's really cute!
Aichi
Aichi.
The president is walking.
It's true!
Chiba
It's so cute!
And a famous country, too.
I see.
Oh, wow.
Wow!
A solo exhibition of a bunch of hair.
It's so cute.
I'm writing a picture book.
You write picture books?
May I?
They're different stories.
I'm trying to get them published.
Cute!
It's cute.
I want it.
I know.
Good luck.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
I knew it! Each one is so unique!
Hey, all of them.
Hello.
Wow.
How do you draw these?
You're right. How do you do that?
How do you draw this?
It's digital.
Yes, it is.
That's great.
Thank you very much.
That's pretty.
Hey.
That's great.
Gals are cute.
Aya's a gal.
No, but...
I love the idea.
This exhibit is like a recreation of that room.
Oh, there's Marika!
And there's Pei-chan, too.
Do you come here all the time?
I'm here all the time.
Hello.
Here's the theme.
We're called Playbros.
There are about 6 of us and we make games.
This one is a game we made together.
We hope you enjoy it!
Thank you very much.
Tilt up, down, right, left, and left only once.
Slide your and your opponent's ice cream
Paint the floor!
Please hold your device flat.
You don't play games, do you?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Vanilla turn
You're the one who tilts the iPad in the direction you want.
Oh, great, great, great!
I've got a little pineapple now.
Mint is in and burped and moved on
Oh, wow.
It's got all kinds of gimmicks.
What do you mean?
Well, it's your turn.
You can type up and down, but it's still in there.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, I got it.
I just bumped into Doria.
You bumped into Doria?
I'm sorry.
The game is played by alternating turns like this.
The one who paints the most coats wins.
I see.
You're going to paint.
Oh...
Oh, oh.
This is...
Oh, wow.
Wrap.
Oh, it's over. I lost so much.
Wow.
Meat wins.
Eh, wow.
He's cute.
Amazing.
It's like.
Eh, interesting.
Thank you.
You can make such nice things, too.
Hey.
Amazing.
I think Aya would like cars.
I like it.
Yes, I do.
What?
What did you do?
You suck at angles, Sakku!
Hey, it's just that...
Shall we do it?
It's so heavy.
It'll be fine.
Come on!
It's a bad angle.
It's a really bad angle.
Sorry.
Shift, shift, shift!
At our flea market, we sell only products made by students themselves.
We sell sculptures, illustration goods, ceramics, aesthetics, and other items that make the most of the strengths of each department.
Wow!
Where do I start?
I wonder if it's portraits or where....
It's still over there!
Hello!
Hello.
Can I get a portrait?
Uh, just this side, please.
Oh, this side.
Lucky mission.
You have 15 seconds to draw an illustration of a randomly drawn subject.
The shopkeeper will guess what you drew.
If you guess correctly, we will pay for the product.
Oh, I heard that you draw an illustration in 15 seconds.
What?
What? I...
That's a lot of work!
It might be nice, but it's okay.
But I'll give it a try.
I want an easy one.
Okay?
Okay, I'll see.
Okay.
Don't go.
All right, let's do it.
One. Two.
Two.
Wait, wait, wait.
Three. Four.
Four.
Five.
Six.
Aya, yeah.
Fifteen.
But you're good, aren't you?
It's only 15.
I don't know.
Okay.
Please.
Glasses.
Yes, sir.
No, no, no, no, no.
Please.
Se-no.
Thank you very much.
How did you know?
I thought it was a horse.
It's perfect.
Yay, I got it.
I'm so happy for you, Ume.
I'm so happy!
So, the mission was a success.
Thank you so much!
It's embarrassing.
I wonder how it'll turn out.
I wonder what they're doing.
I sing and dance in a group called Nogizaka46.
What's your name?
Hot Ayame.
Ayame.
My name is Ayame.
I have one round.
She'll make sure of it.
Ayame, your posture is too good.
I have good posture when I sit down.
Here we go.
I'll look at them all at once.
All together.
That's great.
It's me.
Yes, that's great!
I was so nervous.
I'm glad.
That's great.
Look at you.
That's nice.
She looks nice.
She's a nice lady.
I'm so happy.
It's a phone case.
It's true.
Cute.
Cute, cute, cute.
They're fortune-telling stickers.
There are 12 different kinds of stickers that come out at random.
There's a star in the upper left corner that says "good luck with your studies.
Do you want to try?
I'll give it a try.
I wonder if they'll come out.
You're not that good at drawing, are you, Saki?
I'm not good at it.
Wait a minute.
Why are you doing that?
Well...
Okay...
No, no, no, I can't do it. I can't do it.
I'll go.
Okay.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
even if you don't
You know what I mean?
Here we go.
Seino's
Skateboarding
That's great.
That's amazing.
He's so fast!
He's so good!
You did it!
Thank you very much.
You don't care?
I don't care.
I don't know.
Okay.
You're cute.
Seino.
Good luck at work.
That's great!
Luck at home
Work.
Three stars.
I was 3 stars too.
Luck at work
Get away from what you have to do.
What? Is it okay to run away?
It's okay.
It's okay to run away.
Then let's do our best while running away a little bit.
Question.
How can I clean up my room?
Cute!
But it looks clean.
Me?
Yeah.
I don't know if it's clean.
But I like to clean.
Of course you do.
You write these too?
Oh, yeah.
Wow.
That's amazing.
It's cute.
It's nice.
I'll take it home and treasure it.
Thank you very much.
Oh, there's something here.
Oh, my God, don't tell me you made this, too.
Oh, it's alive.
Hello.
Tamameshi-kun?
My name is Tamamushi.
Tamamushi.
Protecting Tamabi's environment
Heh.
I'm here to protect it.
Thank you very much.
Bye bye
wind house whoa
hmm
English material
that's etto 2
yes a star love
aname
ni in ame
Oh, it's written in English.
Words that make you calm.
Heh.
May I try it on?
Oh, it's perfect!
Oh, that's so nice.
It's so cute.
We should play a game together.
Oh, I want this one. I want this one.
What does it say?
It's a real virtue.
Virtue.
It's gonna be good.
Mission Opportunity, right?
Yeah, it's a mission opportunity.
Oh, can you do it?
Ready?
All right, let's go!
One, two, three.
Fifteen.
I think I got it!
You think you can do it?
Yes!
I'm going for it!
Correct!
Was it easy to understand?
Yes, it was.
Yes, it was!
A coquette!
Yes!
I just lost my ring, and I thought you'd like it.
That's great!
Thank you so much!
I'm so glad!
I think the green one is pretty.
Wow!
The one that looks like a Saki is...
This one!
Let's go this way!
It's too hard!
What? It's not difficult?
I don't get it either, Eratachan.
Here we go! Ready!
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Oh, but I think it's okay.
Here you go.
You know what I mean?
There you go. - Yeah.
Ah, Urashima Taro.
Thank you very much.
Yay!
You got it.
You got it all figured out.
Really?
I'm so glad.
Thank you very much.
Yeah!
I got it!
He's so cute.
How's your stomach?
I'm so hungry.
You can eat.
You don't look hungry, but you are.
I'm hungry enough to eat.
It smells so good.
Would you like to take a picture of it?
Yes, sir.
Oh, my God.
It's true.
Yes, it's a little bit like an art college.
I'd like you to pay attention to the decorations.
I'd like to draw your attention to it.
We make the decorations ourselves, don't we?
We made them ourselves.
How cute!
They have good taste.
It's amazing.
Great grilled chicken!
The decorations are amazing!
It's three dimensional!
I want some!
Let's eat yakitori.
Want some?
Let's eat.
The decorations are so cute.
Do you have a concept?
The concept is called Heisei Retro.
It's something I've seen before.
wiring and vivid colors.
It's a combination of various things.
It's cute, and it's definitely Heisei.
It's amazing!
I don't know if I'm too old for this.
I really admire it.
I really admire you.
Oh, my God!
I got it!
I got it.
Oh, my God.
Let's eat!
Monjiri
The peel
This is for the green onion!
Bon appétit!
Oh, yum!
Oh, it's so good!
Wait a minute.
It's so good!
You idiot!
It's so good it's funny.
It's so good!
Oh, my God.
Oh, wait.
It's so good, but wait a minute.
You're laughing, aren't you?
You're laughing when you say it's delicious.
It's delicious.
Oh, wait.
How can it not be this good?
It's great.
I love the salt.
Salt is good.
Oh, my God! It's so good!
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God.
It's so good!
It's really good.
You can eat as many of these as you want.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Wow, that's so cute.
Yum.
Looks good.
It's kind of stylish, isn't it?
It really is.
It really looks like a café.
It looks like a café.
It looks amazing!
It looks delicious.
One plain waffle.
And one with caramelized nuts.
Yes, sir.
That's all.
That'll be 700 yen.
Yes, sir.
Looks good, it's warm.
Bon appétit!
Delicious!
Crunchy! It's so good!
We've been going around and it's been fun, hasn't it?
It was a lot of fun.
It was the first time for me to really go around, or at least the first time I've properly gone around after the festival.
I was so inspired by all the stores and exhibits that were so well organized!
Everything was handmade!
It was all so beautiful.
You know what?
You were responding.
I'm glad you came.
I'm glad you're here.
Thank you so much again for coming out today.
Thank you very much.
It's been a pleasure.
They're really nice people.
Hey.
Let's wrap it up.
Please subscribe to our channel and give us a high rating.
Thank you so much! Please subscribe!
Bye bye.
by H.